http://mallerbrass.com/privacy-terms/

Privacy Policy & Terms of Use
We value the privacy of our visitors and customers online.
General Disclaimer
While visiting MallerBrass.com, we will not collect any personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. If you choose to provide this information, it will be used for the express purpose for which it was intended, such as responding to your request for information or joining a web discussion forum. We remind you that if you visit a link outside of MallerBrass.com you are subject to the privacy policies of that site.
Information collected and stored automatically
MallerBrass.com automatically collects some technical information from you when you visit the site in order to give you the best possible experience. MallerBrass.com uses web measurement technology (Google Analytics) to automatically track how visitors interact with MallerBrass.com including where they came from, what they did on the site and whether they completed any pre-determined tasks while on the site. This type of usage is classified by the Office of Management and Budget as Tier 2 usage since it is a multi-session web measurement. Aggregate data is used to help Maller Brass improve our user interface and diversify our content offerings to meet the needs of our customers, track operational problems, prevent fraud and improve the effectiveness, security and integrity of the site. This information does not identify you personally and data is only retained in accordance with the Maller Brass data retention policy. For each page that you visit, we collect and store only the following technical information:
Date and time of access
URL address of the MallerBrass.com webpage visited
Internet domain and IP address from which our MallerBrass.com was accessed
Type of browser and operating system used to access our site (if provided by the browser)
URL address of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
Completion or success status of the request for a web page or other on-line item
File size of the webpage visited
This information is only used to help us make the site more useful for you. With this data we learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We never track or record information about individuals and their visits and we do not share this data with anyone outside MallerBrass.com unless necessary for law enforcement purposes.
Cookies
When you visit some MallerBrass.coms, their web servers generate pieces of information known as cookies, which helps webmasters understand how users interact with their site’s content and services. MallerBrass.coms use cookies to track one’s activities on a MallerBrass.com (e.g., pages visited, links clicked on, etc.), and to record information about the user so when the user returns to the site, customized features can be provided.
There are two types of cookies. A session cookie is a line of text that is stored temporarily in your web browser’s memory cache, and will expire when the browser is closed. A session cookie is not placed on any hard drive, and it is destroyed as soon as you close your browser. A persistent cookie is saved to a file on your hard drive and is accessed whenever you re-visit the MallerBrass.com that put it there. This lets that MallerBrass.com remember what you were interested in the last time you visited.
We use persistent cookies to enable Google Analytics to differentiate between new and returning MallerBrass.com visitors. Persistent cookies remain on your computer between visits to MallerBrass.com until they expire. We may also use persistent cookies to block repeated invitations to take the customer satisfaction survey. The persistent cookies that block repeated survey invitations expire in 90 days.
MallerBrass.com may utilize third party services to enhance its distribution of data and information (e.g., videos) through links from the MallerBrass.com web site. A persistent cookie may be set by such a third party provider when you click on the provider’s link in order to access MallerBrass.com data (e.g., play a video).
By default, persistent cookies and web measurement technologies are automatically used when you visit MallerBrass.com. Nevertheless, if you decide to disable or remove cookies from your browser, you will continue to have access to all information and resources on MallerBrass.com.
Information collected from interactive surveys and forms
MallerBrass.com provides interactive forms that let you voluntarily submit personal information (such as your e-mail address, name, or organization). This occurs when you register to join an online community to submit information to web discussion forums, blogs and other community features; registering to receive e-mail updates and newsletters; and sending questions and comments to the MallerBrass.com team. In these cases, all submitted information is used only for the express purposes for which it is provided, and is not made available to any third party.
MallerBrass.com only shares information you voluntarily provide with other government agencies if required by law. MallerBrass.com never collects information or creates individual profiles for commercial marketing. However, when you join an online community and participate in online discussions, your name and other personal information you provide (except e-mail) are viewable by anyone visiting MallerBrass.com, unless you choose not share this information with the public on your user profile page. Any personal information you provide will be protected to the extent permissible under the Freedom of Information Act and Privacy Act.
Electronically submitted information is maintained and destroyed according to the principles of the Federal Records Act and the regulations and records schedules of the National Archives and Records Administration, and in some cases may be covered by the Privacy Act and subject to the Freedom of Information Act. A discussion of your rights under these laws can be found on the Freedom of Information Act home page.
MallerBrass.com may also use online survey instruments to obtain feedback on your experience with MallerBrass.com. The survey initiation pops up for a random sample of visitors, is voluntary and does not collect personal information. If you decline the survey you will still have access to the same information and resources of MallerBrass.com as those who do take the survey. The survey reports are available only to MallerBrass.com managers and other staff who require this information to perform their duties. Maller Brass retains the data from the survey results in accordance with its data retention policy.
Trumpet Resources
Our Facebook
Search for:
Copyright © 2020 Maller Brass. All Rights Reserved.Designed by Cassus Media
